A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1947-1951 FA759
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1951
  - England, 1951; 1951/401
    - England - (I-01), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3587)
    - England - Oxford - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 536, Folder 3588)
    - England - (P-T), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3589)
    - England - (P-T), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3590)
    - England - (P-T), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3591)
    - England - University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3592)
    - England - (T-Z), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
    - England - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/401.A
      - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
    - England - Nursing, 1951; 1951/401.C
      - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/401.E
      - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
    - England - Public Health Education, 1951; 1951/401.L
      - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
    - England - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/401.R
      - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
    - England - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/401.S
      - England, 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3593)
  - Scotland, 1951; 1951/405
    - Scotland - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 537, Folder 3594)
    - Scotland - Scott, Jerome F., 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3666)
    - Scotland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/405.D
      - Scotland, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3595)
    - Scotland - Social Services, 1951; 1951/405.S
      - Scotland, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3595)
  - Australia, 1951; 1951/410
    - Australia - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3596)
    - Australia - Australian National University - Pacific Studies, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3667)
    - Australia - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/410.A
      - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
    - Australia - Nursing, 1951; 1951/410.C
      - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
    - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/410.E
      - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
    - Australia - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/410.R
      - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
    - Australia - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/410.S
      - Australia, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - New Zealand, 1951; 1951/418
    - New Zealand, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
    - New Zealand - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/418.A
      - New Zealand, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
    - New Zealand - Nursing, 1951; 1951/418.C
      - New Zealand, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3597)
  - Caribbean, 1951; 1951/420
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3598)
    - Caribbean Region - Administration, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3599)
  - Guyana, 1951; 1951/423
    - British Guyana, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3600)
  - Canada, 1951; 1951/427
    - Canada - Administration, 1951 (Box 538, Folder 3600)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3601)
    - Canada - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3602)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/427.A
      - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
    - Canada - Nursing, 1951; 1951/427.C
      - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
    - Canada - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/427.E
      - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/427.R
      - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
    - Canada - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/427.S
      - Canada, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3603)
  - Jamaica, 1951; 1951/437
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/437.A
      - Jamaica, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Trinidad, 1951; 1951/451
    - Trinidad, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Sri Lanka, 1951; 1951/462
    - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
    - Sri Lanka - Nursing, 1951; 1951/462.C
      - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
    - Sri Lanka - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/462.E
      - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
    - Sri Lanka - Malaria, 1951; 1951/462.I
      - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
    - Sri Lanka - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/462.S
      - Sri Lanka, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - Hong Kong, 1951; 1951/463
    - Hong Kong, 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3604)
  - India, 1951; 1951/464
    - India - (General) - (A-B), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3605)
    - India - (C-H), 1951 (Box 539, Folder 3606)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3607)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3608)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3609)
    - India - (I-Z), 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3610)
    - India - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/464.A
      - India, 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3611)
    - India - Nursing, 1951; 1951/464.C
      - India, 1951 (Box 540, Folder 3611)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/464.D
      - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/464.E
      - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
    - India - Malaria, 1951; 1951/464.I
      - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
    - India - Yellow Fever, 1951; 1951/464.O
      - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
    - India - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/464.R
      - India, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3612)
  - Pakistan, 1951; 1951/465
    - Pakistan, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
    - Pakistan - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/465.A
      - Pakistan, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
    - Pakistan - Nursing, 1951; 1951/465.C
      - Pakistan, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Burma, 1951; 1951/468
    - Burma - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/468.R
      - Burma, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - Iraq, 1951; 1951/470
    - Iraq, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
    - Iraq - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/470.E
      - Iraq, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
    - Iraq - Social Services, 1951; 1951/470.S
      - Iraq, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3614)
  - New Guinea, 1951; 1951/472
    - New Guinea, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Malaysia, 1951; 1951/473
    - Malaysia, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
    - Malaysia - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/473.A
      - Malaysia, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
    - Malaysia - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/473.R
      - Malaysia, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - Africa, 1951; 1951/475
    - Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
    - Africa - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/475.S
      - Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - East Africa Region, 1951; 1951/477
    - East Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
    - East Africa Region - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/477.A
      - East Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
    - East Africa Region - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/477.E
      - East Africa, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3613)
  - North Africa, 1951; 1951/485
    - North Africa - Administration, 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3615)
    - North Africa - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 541, Folder 3616)
    - North Africa - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/485.A
      - North Africa (Box 541, Folder 3616)
    - North Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/485.E
      - North Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3616)
  - Southern Africa, 1951; 1951/487
    Africa, Southern
    - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617)
    - Southern Africa - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/487.A
      - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
    - Southern Africa - Nursing, 1951; 1951/487.C
      - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
    - Southern Africa - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/487.E
      - Southern Africa, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3617.A)
  - West Africa, 1951; 1951/495
    - West Africa Region, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3618)
  - France, 1951; 1951/500
    - France - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3619)
    - France - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3620)
    - France - University - (A-Z), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3621)
    - France - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/500.A
      - France, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
    - France - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/500.E
      - France, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
    - France - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/500.S
      - France, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - Vietnam, 1951; 1951/509
    - Vietnam, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - Society Islands, 1951; 1951/520
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes Tahiti.
    French Polynesia
    - Tahiti (Society Islands), 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3622)
  - Asia, 1951; 1951/600
    - Asia, 1951 (Box 542, Folder 3623)
  - China, 1951; 1951/601
    - China, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3624)
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/601.E
      - China, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3624)
    - China - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/601.R
      - China, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3624)
  - Taiwan, 1951; 1951/605
    - Taiwan, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3625)
    - Taiwan - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/605.A
      - Taiwan, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3625)
    - Taiwan - Nursing, 1951; 1951/605.C
      - Taiwan, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3625)
  - Japan, 1951; 1951/609
    - Japan - (General) - Administration, 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3626)
    - Japan - (A-I), 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3627)
    - Japan - (J-M), 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3628)
    - Japan - (N-P), 1951 (Box 543, Folder 3629)
    - Japan - (Q-Z), 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3630)
    - Japan - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/609.A
      - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
    - Japan - Nursing, 1951; 1951/609.C
      - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/609.E
      - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
    - Japan - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/609.R
      - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
    - Japan - Social Services, 1951; 1951/609.S
      - Japan, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3631)
  - Korea, 1951; 1951/613
    - Korea, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3632)
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/613.E
      - Korea, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3632)
    - Korea - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/613.R
      - Korea, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3632)
  - Thailand, 1951; 1951/617
    - Thailand, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
    - Thailand - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/617.A
      - Thailand, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
    - Thailand - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/617.R
      - Thailand, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
  - Southeast Asia, 1951; 1951/625
    - Southeast Asia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3633)
  - Holland, 1951; 1951/650
    - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3634)
    - Holland - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/650.A
      - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
    - Holland - Nursing, 1951; 1951/650.C
      - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
    - Holland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/650.E
      - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
    - Holland - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/650.R
      - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
    - Holland - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/650.S
      - Netherlands, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Indonesia, 1951; 1951/652
    - Indonesia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/652.E
      - Indonesia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
    - Indonesia - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/652.R
      - Indonesia, 1951 (Box 544, Folder 3635)
  - Europe, 1951; 1951/700
    - Europe, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3636)
    - Europe - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/700.A
      - Europe, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3636)
    - Europe - Nursing, 1951; 1951/700.C
      - Europe, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3636)
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/700.S
      - Dev-1 Devinney, Leland C. - Diary, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3637)
  - Afghanistan, 1951; 1951/703
    - Afghanistan, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Austria, 1951; 1951/705
    - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Austria - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/705.A
      - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Austria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/705.D
      - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Austria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/705.E
      - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Austria - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/705.S
      - Austria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Belgium, 1951; 1951/707
    - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/707.A
      - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Belgium - Nursing, 1951; 1951/707.C
      - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Belgium - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/707.R
      - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
    - Belgium - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/707.S
      - Belgium, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3638)
  - Yugoslavia, 1951; 1951/710
    - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
    - Yugoslavia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/710.D
      - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/710.E
      - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
    - Yugoslavia - Public Health Education, 1951; 1951/710.L
      - Yugoslavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3639)
  - Bulgaria, 1951; 1951/711
    - Bulgaria, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1951; 1951/712
    - Czechoslovakia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Denmark, 1951; 1951/713
    - Denmark, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
    - Denmark - Nursing, 1951; 1951/713.C
      - Denmark, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/713.E
      - Denmark, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Iceland, 1951; 1951/715
    - Iceland, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
    - Iceland - Tuberculosis, 1951; 1951/715.T
      - Iceland, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Scandinavia, 1951; 1951/716
    - Scandinavia, 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3640)
  - Germany, 1951; 1951/717
    - Germany - (General) - (A-G), 1951 (Box 545, Folder 3641)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3642)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3643)
    - Germany - (H-Z), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3644)
    - Germany - Institute for International Educational Research, Frankfurt, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3668)
    - Germany - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/717.A
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1951; 1951/717.D
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/717.E
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/717.S
      - Germany, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Greece, 1951; 1951/749
    - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
    - Greece - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/749.E
      - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
    - Greece - Malaria, 1951; 1951/749.I
      - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
    - Greece - Health Services, 1951; 1951/749.K
      - Greece, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3645)
  - Hungary, 1951; 1951/750
    - Hungary, 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3646)
  - Italy, 1951; 1951/751
    - Italy - (A-P), 1951 (Box 546, Folder 3647)
    - Italy - (Q-Z), 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3648)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/751.A
      - Italy, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/751.E
      - Italy, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Norway, 1951; 1951/767
    - Norway, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/767.E
      - Norway, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Latvia, 1951; 1951/768
    - Latvia, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3649)
  - Iran, 1951; 1951/771
    - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
    - Iran - Anglo-Iranian Oil Co., 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3669)
    - Iran - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/771.A
      - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
    - Iran - Nursing, 1951; 1951/771.C
      - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
    - Iran - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/771.E
      - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
    - Iran - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/771.R
      - Iran, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3650)
      - Iran, 1951 (Box 549, Folder 3669)
  - Portugal, 1951; 1951/773
    - Portugal, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1951; 1951/773.C
      - Portugal, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Romania, 1951; 1951/783
    - Romania, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - USSR, 1951; 1951/785
    - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
    - USSR - Nursing, 1951; 1951/785.C
      - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
    - USSR - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/785.E
      - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
    - USSR - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/785.S
      - USSR, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Poland, 1951; 1951/789
    - Poland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Spain, 1951; 1951/795
    - Spain, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
    - Spain - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/795.E
      - Spain, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3651)
  - Sweden, 1951; 1951/800
    - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
    - Sweden - Nursing, 1951; 1951/800.C
      - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/800.E
      - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/800.R
      - Sweden, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3652)
  - Switzerland, 1951; 1951/803
    - Switzerland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3653)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/803.E
      - Switzerland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3653)
    - Switzerland - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/803.R
      - Switzerland, 1951 (Box 547, Folder 3653)
  - Near East Region, 1951; 1951/804
    - Near East, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Turkey, 1951; 1951/805
    - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
    - Turkey - Nursing, 1951; 1951/805.C
      - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/805.E
      - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
    - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/805.R
      - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
    - Turkey - Social Sciences, 1951; 1951/805.S
      - Turkey, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3654)
  - Israel, 1951; 1951/825
    - Israel, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3655)
    - Israel - Malaria, 1951; 1951/825.I
      - Israel, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3655)
  - Lebanon, 1951; 1951/833
    - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3656)
    - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1951; 1951/833.A
      - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1951; 1951/833.C
      - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1951; 1951/833.E
      - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)
    - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 1951; 1951/833.R
      - Lebanon, 1951 (Box 548, Folder 3657)